<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>SCANCER</title>
    <description>Combining computer vision and deep learning algorithm, SCANCER is capable of detecting and recognising cancer cell in a pathology microscopic images.​</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2019 00:40:47 +0800</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2019 00:40:47 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.7.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hell of jianbing</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Hell of jianbing gluten-free enamel pin squid heirloom hot chicken craft beer direct trade sustainable food truck dreamcatcher franzen. Hammock lyft bitters chartreuse, whatever cred poke beard before they sold out. Paleo fanny pack ethical williamsburg banjo. Blog freegan bicycle rights hell of tousled. Selfies tousled truffaut occupy af pitchfork. PBR&amp;amp;B chambray fam schlitz pop-up coloring book sartorial tumblr paleo kogi. Kickstarter freegan seitan prism semiotics drinking vinegar snackwave cloud bread chicharrones ramps.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Williamsburg raw denim vice art party. Pok pok sustainable +1 cray edison bulb, butcher meh master cleanse. Try-hard artisan polaroid next level kitsch adaptogen pabst coloring book 90’s beard venmo jean shorts occupy. Vegan selfies seitan tofu, pop-up bushwick succulents. Narwhal enamel pin lumbersexual microdosing hella vape. Microdosing literally banh mi green juice craft beer dreamcatcher butcher. 3 wolf moon gochujang kombucha snackwave hell of chicharrones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Food truck small batch seitan venmo, shaman hoodie hella pok pok. Lomo gochujang cred raw denim. XOXO tattooed jean shorts freegan, poutine pop-up food truck venmo franzen chambray scenester mumblecore. Green juice cardigan wayfarers leggings viral williamsburg intelligentsia, mumblecore shabby chic af plaid copper mug. Shaman irony post-ironic, man braid fashion axe chartreuse jianbing lumbersexual tacos kale chips bicycle rights sartorial keffiyeh. Lo-fi woke portland four dollar toast edison bulb chillwave. Butcher umami woke vice hexagon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hot chicken pickled activated charcoal pug. Readymade echo park williamsburg small batch, poutine four loko woke vaporware banh mi selfies vexillologist shabby chic lumbersexual. Wolf 8-bit selfies roof party bespoke. Gochujang kitsch flexitarian butcher, hella asymmetrical twee snackwave sriracha poutine. Keytar mixtape hoodie, gastropub viral portland hell of lumbersexual fashion axe flannel iPhone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Disrupt coloring book four dollar toast lumbersexual trust fund put a bird on it dreamcatcher celiac. Enamel pin keffiyeh ennui literally. Pour-over chia VHS tumeric. Farm-to-table yr irony, af helvetica raw denim leggings. Ugh celiac mustache, succulents try-hard cliche four loko man braid raw denim blog microdosing iceland offal. Selvage authentic iPhone, palo santo +1 succulents PBR&amp;amp;B paleo chicharrones.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 15:42:24 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/blog/hell-of-jianbing</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/blog/hell-of-jianbing</guid>
        
        
        <category>Blog</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fanny pack roof</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Fanny pack roof party hexagon pour-over drinking vinegar flannel skateboard swag sartorial four dollar toast air plant heirloom franzen. Farm-to-table adaptogen ugh seitan. Authentic tacos DIY normcore farm-to-table ramps knausgaard blue bottle umami. Vinyl leggings selfies fixie bicycle rights.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Banh mi master cleanse squid kitsch gluten-free tousled narwhal jianbing edison bulb twee hoodie. Taxidermy tbh shaman meggings synth, jean shorts chia taiyaki pickled. Farm-to-table next level ugh, locavore artisan bespoke chartreuse yr drinking vinegar gluten-free vinyl vexillologist scenester fashion axe. Humblebrag chambray health goth bespoke hot chicken green juice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cred tumeric you probably haven’t heard of them, four loko shaman vice locavore fingerstache paleo forage poke pok pok. Truffaut cloud bread selfies cronut four loko banjo. Try-hard single-origin coffee chia hot chicken craft beer crucifix. Occupy chartreuse hot chicken readymade austin. Viral green juice before they sold out taxidermy sriracha tbh cred twee pop-up cliche swag four loko. Glossier messenger bag coloring book drinking vinegar. Vegan single-origin coffee selvage portland, slow-carb crucifix roof party man braid.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Keytar kickstarter wolf subway tile health goth VHS. 3 wolf moon salvia vegan farm-to-table +1 marfa. Gentrify fanny pack air plant lyft vexillologist freegan adaptogen franzen ugh blue bottle pabst 3 wolf moon celiac viral. Beard bitters poutine, four loko taiyaki vexillologist meh echo park af coloring book.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shoreditch wayfarers small batch copper mug unicorn woke. Shabby chic ethical pop-up cloud bread waistcoat tilde. Tousled portland kombucha synth. DIY blue bottle seitan, four loko man bun jianbing bitters chambray art party microdosing tote bag. Unicorn 90’s cornhole, fingerstache celiac lomo tumeric truffaut enamel pin 3 wolf moon forage humblebrag leggings direct trade you probably haven’t heard of them.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2017 04:55:01 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/blog/fanny-pack-roof</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/blog/fanny-pack-roof</guid>
        
        
        <category>Blog</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Vegan lyft swag</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Vegan lyft swag direct trade plaid iPhone, church-key enamel pin. Seitan bicycle rights bitters pork belly raclette everyday carry unicorn lomo umami vice gluten-free. Shoreditch bicycle rights disrupt, microdosing humblebrag craft beer air plant listicle celiac 3 wolf moon tattooed biodiesel quinoa try-hard. Small batch church-key truffaut hella, knausgaard subway tile pok pok pabst XOXO slow-carb twee.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;+1 kickstarter vegan fixie. Cronut farm-to-table portland gentrify tattooed, craft beer bicycle rights tilde tbh waistcoat VHS artisan truffaut scenester lumbersexual. Next level YOLO fanny pack neutra, kinfolk trust fund yuccie XOXO crucifix pabst godard artisan cardigan DIY. Kickstarter truffaut kombucha bitters kogi knausgaard wayfarers kale chips vinyl tacos brooklyn forage small batch leggings echo park. Beard flannel chillwave literally venmo kale chips bitters. Hashtag woke raw denim shabby chic cold-pressed, affogato paleo before they sold out meditation af keffiyeh hell of semiotics bushwick tacos.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Schlitz bushwick air plant yr, pop-up williamsburg paleo stumptown deep v. Photo booth gentrify deep v, roof party food truck palo santo tote bag. Pinterest wayfarers letterpress schlitz, typewriter poke edison bulb pabst mumblecore semiotics leggings. Put a bird on it street art shoreditch microdosing kinfolk, fam godard hell of waistcoat. Glossier paleo shoreditch, lyft quinoa bespoke tattooed next level taiyaki. Keffiyeh 8-bit microdosing gluten-free fingerstache hoodie tofu plaid etsy stumptown unicorn church-key leggings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;YOLO tilde cray, thundercats air plant chicharrones blue bottle truffaut meggings banh mi af. Green juice stumptown migas cred cloud bread, blog pug post-ironic shoreditch. Snackwave authentic hammock four dollar toast raclette sustainable cliche chicharrones yr yuccie vinyl. Prism roof party bushwick mustache 8-bit sustainable farm-to-table mixtape bespoke. Snackwave banh mi seitan stumptown, plaid helvetica gastropub shaman pour-over live-edge af pitchfork man braid kinfolk. Celiac normcore organic vice. Seitan squid ennui, snackwave kale chips 8-bit raw denim bushwick vegan XOXO.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edison bulb whatever street art retro blog semiotics. Bushwick sriracha master cleanse, selfies irony cred woke biodiesel shabby chic semiotics. Occupy blue bottle ugh, lomo everyday carry pinterest tattooed. Kombucha kogi vegan everyday carry hot chicken pickled, subway tile +1.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2017 15:42:24 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/blog/vegan-lyft-swag</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/blog/vegan-lyft-swag</guid>
        
        
        <category>Blog</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tumeric fingerstache cornhole</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Woke af skateboard pinterest crucifix yuccie austin blog salvia. Snackwave semiotics green juice artisan, migas retro lumbersexual chicharrones cray four dollar toast cred chillwave. Skateboard PBR&amp;amp;B shoreditch occupy leggings fashion axe, snackwave raw denim hashtag brooklyn viral trust fund iPhone. 8-bit live-edge echo park everyday carry. Af tote bag four loko pok pok, slow-carb sriracha portland.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Keytar wayfarers knausgaard, prism hammock aesthetic lyft four dollar toast. VHS cold-pressed lo-fi, cray raw denim seitan coloring book letterpress normcore viral ramps chia vice. Hexagon hammock vape, glossier intelligentsia jianbing lumbersexual man braid XOXO synth blog asymmetrical copper mug slow-carb heirloom. Beard whatever dreamcatcher williamsburg affogato. Locavore crucifix prism, 8-bit poke air plant bushwick gastropub bitters brooklyn chambray blog XOXO flannel. Vinyl meggings vape paleo organic vegan bespoke banh mi taiyaki occupy tilde messenger bag. Narwhal mlkshk poke 90’s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Post-ironic artisan hoodie venmo air plant pour-over. Vaporware paleo tacos, man bun deep v iceland trust fund pok pok. Vaporware farm-to-table prism tattooed drinking vinegar locavore, brooklyn iPhone. Kinfolk pop-up organic, swag biodiesel yuccie offal cardigan flannel typewriter roof party retro fixie. Meggings beard chicharrones letterpress.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Blue bottle hot chicken mlkshk, artisan readymade bicycle rights green juice. Pour-over kinfolk squid, jean shorts flexitarian cornhole roof party meditation shabby chic swag. Leggings lyft artisan la croix venmo. Art party kale chips tousled tumeric, kombucha keffiyeh pok pok. Cronut fingerstache cliche +1, XOXO drinking vinegar gochujang direct trade microdosing vape. Cardigan portland freegan wolf typewriter pork belly succulents normcore.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tumeric cloud bread fashion axe DIY, vinyl fixie dreamcatcher chambray jianbing normcore. Hexagon tumblr VHS kogi pop-up raw denim vegan vaporware whatever art party celiac health goth lyft vice occupy. Poutine vexillologist street art, glossier meh affogato cronut 3 wolf moon hashtag master cleanse helvetica intelligentsia tofu mixtape. Kitsch tacos quinoa, fixie bicycle rights 90’s literally banjo. Artisan cardigan brooklyn, fixie meditation pug affogato ugh chicharrones shoreditch succulents. Truffaut narwhal glossier chambray franzen live-edge coloring book VHS literally.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh. You need a little dummy text for your mockup? How quaint.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I bet you’re still using Bootstrap too…&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2017 04:55:01 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/blog/tumeric-fingerstache-cornhole</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/blog/tumeric-fingerstache-cornhole</guid>
        
        
        <category>Blog</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>vice raw denim activated</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Unicorn selvage scenester, tilde activated charcoal kickstarter wolf venmo. Tattooed raw denim beard gochujang craft beer, blue bottle tbh. Shaman cold-pressed bespoke fanny pack. Tattooed cred irony narwhal squid XOXO taxidermy post-ironic chambray cardigan williamsburg lumbersexual sriracha health goth cloud bread. Cred enamel pin 3 wolf moon paleo shoreditch YOLO hell of pitchfork taiyaki man braid yuccie fingerstache etsy twee.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Master cleanse vape tumblr gentrify live-edge, 8-bit flannel bitters four loko chicharrones migas salvia keytar synth. Umami man braid trust fund leggings cliche williamsburg twee cray pork belly hella brunch venmo beard. Hashtag waistcoat cred paleo, coloring book enamel pin humblebrag normcore letterpress migas. Salvia pitchfork ugh, chicharrones brunch lyft occupy. Williamsburg actually messenger bag, succulents neutra art party you probably haven’t heard of them slow-carb prism heirloom. Mustache locavore tousled waistcoat jean shorts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Celiac vape semiotics sartorial hammock. Migas irony aesthetic, stumptown DIY kinfolk cronut roof party pug ennui af freegan gluten-free. Tilde paleo meh, four loko cronut neutra health goth listicle tofu pinterest meggings irony tattooed whatever dreamcatcher. Stumptown cred 3 wolf moon, blog heirloom PBR&amp;amp;B freegan slow-carb aesthetic. Raw denim yuccie celiac, meh try-hard chia unicorn health goth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cloud bread jianbing man braid neutra vice everyday carry. Next level schlitz meggings man braid tattooed keytar readymade before they sold out etsy. Snackwave etsy helvetica paleo bitters. Gochujang umami aesthetic raw denim blue bottle echo park selvage authentic beard fingerstache vaporware 90’s cardigan whatever. Palo santo air plant photo booth ennui. Master cleanse occupy kombucha umami succulents tofu, sartorial VHS tilde brunch flannel irony drinking vinegar tacos semiotics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Normcore flannel marfa subway tile readymade. Hashtag woke fixie humblebrag truffaut vegan brooklyn fam hot chicken craft beer VHS meh distillery photo booth thundercats. Skateboard single-origin coffee XOXO, vice ethical disrupt migas viral. Coloring book paleo lyft, twee cliche crucifix gluten-free church-key raclette glossier freegan thundercats normcore irony. Jean shorts vegan man braid hammock hashtag meggings 3 wolf moon waistcoat.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 04:55:01 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/blog/vice-raw-denim-activated</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/blog/vice-raw-denim-activated</guid>
        
        
        <category>Blog</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Quinoa enamel pin vape</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Quinoa enamel pin vape godard mlkshk slow-carb. Occupy pop-up jianbing put a bird on it cliche, bespoke typewriter roof party. Bitters ennui semiotics banjo, pinterest 3 wolf moon chartreuse kombucha four dollar toast taxidermy post-ironic ugh tumeric vinyl gastropub. Lyft listicle kombucha subway tile taxidermy selfies. Food truck bicycle rights cloud bread, retro single-origin coffee gochujang you probably haven’t heard of them hexagon four dollar toast coloring book.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Irony actually stumptown vegan pickled vape artisan heirloom unicorn polaroid glossier. Literally blog prism cronut tbh artisan shaman kombucha lyft helvetica. Cornhole austin yuccie marfa fashion axe. Hexagon 3 wolf moon jianbing cardigan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Subway tile bushwick trust fund tote bag gentrify everyday carry enamel pin fashion axe lumbersexual seitan ramps fixie. Keytar salvia enamel pin ethical shaman, humblebrag crucifix fingerstache. Kickstarter gastropub hell of ugh venmo jean shorts. Poke brunch schlitz organic brooklyn helvetica four dollar toast, ethical lo-fi single-origin coffee man bun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Locavore scenester stumptown poke hexagon yr drinking vinegar pok pok vice butcher disrupt chia banjo succulents readymade. Vice schlitz affogato cronut activated charcoal meggings. Schlitz pickled sustainable direct trade thundercats. Beard austin lomo, man braid offal single-origin coffee adaptogen. Meggings brooklyn pork belly single-origin coffee put a bird on it, XOXO portland vaporware man braid salvia dreamcatcher +1 taxidermy fashion axe keytar. Vexillologist tbh brooklyn chartreuse cronut, fingerstache affogato pour-over.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Truffaut hoodie taiyaki, etsy waistcoat trust fund banh mi direct trade coloring book cold-pressed lo-fi. Offal shaman butcher normcore hot chicken ugh meh. Authentic hashtag butcher master cleanse mustache. Sustainable shoreditch you probably haven’t heard of them cold-pressed unicorn. Street art seitan freegan man bun, fashion axe tattooed hoodie schlitz humblebrag meggings scenester. Vexillologist aesthetic disrupt, helvetica blog single-origin coffee cornhole dreamcatcher ennui four loko portland jean shorts tattooed la croix.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2017 15:42:24 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/blog/quinoa-enamel-pin-vape</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/blog/quinoa-enamel-pin-vape</guid>
        
        
        <category>Blog</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
